Finding Aid for the Doreen Gehry Nelson Method of Design-Based Learning (formerly City Building Education™) Records LSC.2239
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Center for City Building Education™ Files
  - People
    This subseries includes correspondence from CBE trustees, teachers, consultants, designers, architects, museum curators, former students, and federal officials. Files are arranged in alphabetical order by surname.
    - Bloom, Benjamin (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Brown, Stephen (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Clowes, Dr. Richard (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Coates, Gary (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - de Bretteville, Sheila (Box 9, Folder 19)
      In addition to typed and handwritten letters from de Bretteville, materials include her curriculum vitae and a "Judy's back in town!" invitation for a celebration in honor of Judy Chicago who founded The Woman's Building in Los Angeles with de Bretteville and Arlene Raven in 1973.
    - Eames, Charles (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Eames, Ray (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Eisenman, Peter (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Fleischmann, Ernest (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Fuller, Buckminster (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Gehry, Frank O. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Goodlad, Dean (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Green, Nancye (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton, Susan (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Hawley, Anne (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Hawley, Peter (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Heckman, Paul (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Hernandez, Jorge (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Hierbert, Ruth (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Hosoda, Hiroko (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Huey, Don (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Koshalek, Richard (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Mandell, Alan and Liz (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Oldenburg, Claes (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Olney, David (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Omohundro, Watson (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Preminger (Wiseman), Judy (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Rice, Kathleen Brown (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Rickman, Rebecca (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Rockefeller, David Jr. (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Rosser, Phyllis (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Salk, Jonas (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Stoltz, Leslie (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Taylor, Anne (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Tucker, Dr. Eugene (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Weisman, Marcia (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Wurman, Richard Saul (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1969-1978, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 26-29)
    - Children's correspondence (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Parent's correspondence (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Significant personnel
    This subseries includes correspondence, personnel files, contracts, and resumes from former CBE staff and consultants. These files are arranged according to Nelson's existing order.
    - Past staff employees (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - CBE personnel, 1975-2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - CBE resumes, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Career Ed., 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
    - Past consultant employees (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Baizely, Doris (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Benjamin, Dan (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Boorstin, Jon (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Browne, Nancy (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Fox, Terri (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Gardner, Diana (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Hoesli, Marjean (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Letelier, Jose (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Mechur, Ralph (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Moreland, Doug (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Oliker, Ditta (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Alexis (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Stayner, Gil (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Weisbach, Gerald (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Implementation
    This subseries consists of evaluations, reading and mathematics tests, teacher test manuals, standardized test scores, testimonials, lesson plans, transcriptions of reflective discussions and statistical reports concerning the implementation of CBE methodologies at sites such as Sulphur Springs Union School District, ABC Unified School District, California State University (CSU) Long Beach, CSU Dominguez Hills, CSU Los Angeles and in collaboration with the American Bar Association (ABA).
    - Sulphur Springs evaluations, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
      Materials include standardized math and reading tests, answer keys, test scores and evaluation reports.
    - Experience reports, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Materials include two reports by teacher Eleanor Hughes on the effectiveness of CBE workshops.
    - Final evaluation copies, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Materials include two final evaluation copies by students of the City Building/Career Education Program.
    - Evaluation reports, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
      Materials include City Building Career Education Program evaluation reports for classes at CSU Long Beach, CSU Dominguez Hills and CSU Los Angeles.
    - CB joint sessions final evaluation copy, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - CSULA Anthropology final evaluations, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Instant City Project evaluations, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Adrianne Bank's evaluation report, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - North Monterey U.S.D. evaluation report, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Book II experience reports, 1973-1980 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - CBE testimonials, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Cerritos Elementary School discussion transcript, 1981 May 19 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Nelson interview transcipts, 1981 December 14 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
    - Lesson plan maps, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Japan testimonial, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Materials include correspondence from Hiroko Hosoda of the Architecture and Children Network Sendai concerning appreciation for CBE lectures and workshops in Sendai, children's conference buttons, object transformation drawings, a map of Japan and a poster with an illustration of a woman driving a car with two passengers hanging on in the back seat. One passenger exclaims, "No! No!" to which the driver responds, "Sorry, Sorry, I'm a woman driver."
    - 6 1/2 steps manuals, undated (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
      Folder 13 includes two copies of 6 1/2 steps to Academic Achievement through Backwards Thinking™ City Building Education™ by Doreen Nelson with Leslie Stoltz.
      Folder 14 includes overheads of the manual for presentations.
    - Sections of From Stones to Skyscrapers, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - The Children's Evaluation, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - ABA files, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 1-12)
      Materials concern the implementation of CBE in collaboration with the American Bar Association (ABA).
    - ABC files, 1978-1983 (Box 15, Folder 1-11, Box 14, Folder 13-16, Box 16, Folder 1-2)
      These records document CBE implementation within the ABC Unified School District.
      Box 14: Materials include project proposals, meeting minutes, diagrams and correspondence with the district (1980-1982).
      Box 15: Materials include long range training plans, evaluations, transcripts of discussions and workshops, charts, handouts, workshop agendas, press, program and correspondence concerning the Classroom City Demonstration/Workshop at the Biltmore Hotel for the CCAIA convention and experience reports for the United States Office of Education (1979-1983).
      Box 16: Materials include evaluations, ABC Community Learning Center Prospectus, consultant reports and a USOE Environmental Education Annual Report(1978-1980).
    - Norwalk-La Mirada USD, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Materials include inter-office district memos, mentor teacher instructional strategies and a CBE tour invitation.
    - Arts, Education, Americans, 1976 February 13 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      One audio cassette.
      Materials include correspondence, a transcript of Nelson's speech before the Rockefeller Panel on "The Arts, Education and Americans," and an audiocassette recording of the panel.
    - Education Tomorrow conversations, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
      Materials include transcripts of national figures in conversation with Doreen Nelson and David Rockefeller, Jr. about "The Future of Learning and Schooling in America; U.S. Education Tomorrow: Barebones or Basics?"
    - Career Education files, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 8-10, Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      Box 16: Materials include a United States Office of Education (USOE) application for Federal assistance, reports on City Building career education programs on California State University (CSU) campuses, correspondence and program press clippings.
      Box 17: Materials include correspondence, experience reports and final reports for City Building career education programs at CSU Los Angeles, CSU Long Beach and CSU Dominguez Hills.
    - Chaular Summer Project, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Materials include a report from the Chaular Elementary School Bilingual Coordinator concerning its Migrant Education Summer Program work with CBE.
    - Compton, 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
      Materials include experience reports for Compton Elementary School and El Segundo Elementary School.
    - Long Beach, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Materials include experience reports for College Intermediate Elementary School.
    - Lowell Massachusetts, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Materials include correspondence, Harvard Professor Dennis Reinhardt's resume and plans for Lowell Massachusetts Public School System involvement with CBE.
    - Maryland Project, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Materials include correspondence, abstract and budget for CBEP's work with the Law-Related Education Program for the Schools of Maryland, Inc.
    - Migrant Education, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
      Materials include student work samples, evaluations and migrant education Stanford Project program descriptions.
    - Monterey, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
      Materials include experience reports, proposals and consultant agreements concerning CBE as an alternative approach to bilingual education within the North Monterey County Unified School District. This work was sponsored by the Migrant Education Region I Office, directed by Eduardo Cabrera.
    - Prospectus, 1981-1984; Materials include the Center for City Building Prospectus and CBE Prospectus Synopsis. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - USD files, 1971-1985 (Box 18, Folder 1-13)
      Materials include correspondence, evaluations and standardized assessments for CBE work with Unified School Districts such as Inglewood, Compton, Long Beach, L.A. City Schools, Montebello, Norwalk/La Mirada, Pasadena, Santa Monica and Sulphur Springs.
    - Course files, 1973-1997 (Box 18, Folder 14-17)
      Materials include correspondence, reports and curriculum plans for CBE courses and workshops at various USDs, UCLA Extension, Walker Art Center and Otis/Parsons.
    - Japan files, 1993-1999 (Box 21, Folder 1-2, Box 19, Folder 1-10, Box 20, Folder 1-3)
      Box 19: Materials include correspondence, photos, maps, newsletters, brochures, magazines and Architecture and Children publications concerning a Japanese - United States cultural and educational grass roots exchange program between the Center for City Building Education and the Architecture and Children Network of Sendai (1993-1997).
      Box 20: Materials include Japanese publications, reports, correspondence with Hiroko Hosada of Network Sendai and a photo album (1996-1998).
      Box 21: Materials include Architecture and Children Network of Sendai newsletters and report books, letters from Japanese students, Sendai City Board of Education reports and correspondence from Hisako Kaihatsu of Kyoto Research Park (1998-1999).
    - ROP files, 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 3-7, Box 22, Folder 1-8)
      These East San Gabriel Valley Regional Occupational Program (ROP) files document CBE's staff development and curriculum assistance work shops.
      Box 21: Materials include evaluations, sign-in sheets, lesson plans, agendas, worksheets, consultant services agreements and ROP final reports (1997-2000).
      Box 22: Materials include evaluations, final reports, agendas, correspondence, a print out of a presentation by Laurel Adler and a Small Learning Communities (SLC) grant application (2000-2003).
  - Grant proposals, 1971-2012
    This subseries includes grant proposals arranged in the existing chronological order of the creator by year and then chronologically by unit or type which include University, Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education (FIPSE), and National Endowment for the Arts (NEA).
    The following are common file title acronyms:
    ARCO - Atlantic Richfield Company
    A.I.S.C. - Artists in Schools and Communities
    C.A.C. - California Arts Commission
    C.C.F. - California Community Foundation
    FIPSE - Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education
    O.E.G. - Office of Education Grant
    U.S.O.E. - United States Office of Education
    In order to retain the creator's existing order, this subseries also includes handbooks, booklets, and magazines related to grant proposals.
    - U.S.O.E., 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - N.E.A., 1971 September-1972 June (Box 23, Folder 2-5)
      Folder 2: September 1971-June 1972
      Folder 3: January 1972-January 1973
      Folder 4: September 1971-April 1972
      Folder 5: September 1971-June 1972
    - O.E.G., 1972 July-1973 June (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - N.E.A.-U.S.O.E., 1972 September-1973 June (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - N.E.A., 1972 September-1973 June (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - C.A.C., 1973 June-July (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Summer program proposal, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Grant proposal - museum setting, circa 1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - C.A.C., 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - N.E.A., 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - C.A.C., 1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - N.E.A., 1974 May-1974 November (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Communications and environmental arts, 1974 June-1974 August (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - N.E.A., 1974 June-1975 June (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - N.E.A. grant film, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - U.S.O.E., 1975 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Career Education, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - C.A.C., 1975 June-1975 September (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - C.A.C. - Artists-In-Communities (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - N.E.A., 1975 June-1976 June (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - A Handbook for City Spirit Facilitators, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      City Spirit is an N.E.A. program initiated to develop a new involvement for the arts in community life. The handbook's reading list includes Nelson's City Building Educational Program because it "...covers extremely well the whole field of working with groups in process."
    - N.E.A., 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - C.A.C., 1977 January-December (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - By Design: A Ten-Year Report, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      This N.E.A. report was generated by the Architecture and Environmental Arts Program.
    - C.A.C. (A.I.S.C.), 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Career education, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - C.A.C. (A.I.S.C.) (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - N.E.A., 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Marine science, 1977 August-1978 August (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Environmental education, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - N.E.A., 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Learning About the Built Environment, circa 1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      This N.E.A. booklet features selected Design Arts Program grants. The CBEP's educational gaming project is described on page 61.
    - C.A.C., 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
    - N.E.A., 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
      Materials include an N.E.A. magazine which features Design Arts recognized grants.
    - C.C.F., 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - C.A.C., 1981 September-1983 June (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
    - N.E.A., 1981 July-1983 December (Box 25, Folder 11, Box 26, Folder 1-2)
      Box 25: July 1981-December 1983
      Box 26: July 1982-December 1982
    - ARCO, 1983 June (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Parsons report, 1983 July (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - N.E.A., 1983 July-1984 July (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic Richfield, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - C.C.F., 1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - N.E.A., 1984 May-1985 April, 1993 November-1996 September (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
    - Buckner $, 1993-2007 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Create-Online.com, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Heller Charitable, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Olmos, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - University, 2000 January-2012 March (Box 27, Folder 1-26)
      These California State Polytechnic University, Pomona grant proposals are for professional development, creative activities, and travel.
    - FIPSE, 1982, 1998, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 1-5)
      FIPSE proposals include A Teacher Peer-Training Program and Lab/Idea Bank, the CREATE/Online project, and Teachers as Designers.
    - N.E.A., 1998-2002, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 6-11)
  - Student work samples, 1959-1982
    This subseries includes specimens of student work arranged in the existing chronological order.
    - University Elementary School, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - MLK poem, 1968 February (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Young Writers of Venice, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - "School on a Bus" drawings, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Letters to the L.A. Times, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Homework books, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
      Nelson kept these books from her first class as examples.
    - Roger's journal, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Homework, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Original stories of houses, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Letters to Councilman Braude, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - House assignment, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Where I want to live assignment, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Natural and man-made objects table of contents, circa 1970 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      This folder includes a contact sheet of images of students and their buildings. Samples of these buildings may be found in boxes 32-34.
    - Open spaces assignment, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Explanations assignment, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - City Planning - Past, Present and Future, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Westminster School work, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 18-20)
      Folders include a variety of sample assignments, class work, and homework by Westminster Elementary School students.
    - ABC visit homework, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Legends, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Building descriptions, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Oakwood plan, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Materials include a binder of city plans entitled Official Record for the City of Venice from the Office of the City Clerk.
    - Typed Oakwood plans, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Trip to the beach stories, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Toy Trains reports, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Diaries, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Monuments of Oakwood homework, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Purium City: Don't want & Need, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Adler and Sullivan posters, circa 1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - CB vocabulary worksheet, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Good and bad environments homework, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      This assignment involved students taking photographs of good and bad environments. Contact sheets are attached to these assignments.
    - Recreation centers assignment, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - City planning worksheets, circa 1972 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Original stories about objects, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - City signs, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Trip We Have Taken assignment, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Change activities, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Fruit store assignment, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Antoni Gaudi report, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Visual daily journal, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Kid stories, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      These handwritten stories were the originals used for Book 1. Some assignments include contact sheets.
    - Final building descriptions, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Limericks, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Composition book, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Community surveys, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Future city posters, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Clan plans, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Who Am I? assignments, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      Materials include a contact sheet of student images.
    - Cerritos Times front page, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Sketch drawings, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - D-4 laws and booklets, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Mayor sign, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Sound and motion posters, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - City buildings, circa 1970s (Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 109)
      City Buildings include the following: Two partial circles made of Styrofoam, painted white surround a painted circle with a hamburger on top. Each of the three pieces is adorned with a fabric border. Structures also include a brown Styrofoam hand, a toothpick building, a peace sign, a red and gold dome topped with a Styrofoam ball and blue feather and a floral canopy. Box 109 contains an oversize peace sign.
  - Selected workshops, 1972-1990
    This subseries includes lesson plans, summaries, participant work samples, reports, guides, handbooks, contracts, correspondence, brochures, evaluations, programs, and agendas regarding CBE workshops and related presentations.
    - Saugus, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Smithsonian workshops, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
    - Aspen Design Conference, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Sulphur Springs U.S.D., 1973-1980 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Smithsonian workshop, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
    - Futures workshop, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Artists-in-Schools program, 1974 July (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - CSBA/ACSA conference, 1974 December (Box 35, Folder 10)
      This California School Boards Association (CSBA) and Association of California School Administrators (ACSA) conference marks the first time in its history that school districts were allowed to display educational programs alongside commercial exhibits.
    - Mini workshop, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - CACE conference, 1975 March (Box 35, Folder 12)
      Materials include a California Association of Compensatory Education (CACE) conference program which features Nelson's workshop, "Application of Academic Skills Through Environmental and Future Oriented Simulation" based on her work with Compton Unified School District.
    - Childhood City workshop, 1975 April (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Summer workshop, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Artists-In-Schools conference, 1975 July (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Education of the Gifted conference, 1975 December (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Montebello workshop, 1976 January 15 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - CAG workshop, 1976 February (Box 35, Folder 18)
      Materials include a California Association for the Gifted (CAG) conference program which features Nelson's two hour program, "City Building Educational Program: A Core Curriculum Integrating Skills of Future Thinking (Invention), Interaction, and Planning."
    - ACSA conference, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Santa Monica workshop, 1976 May (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - A.I.A. convention, 1976 May 3-5 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Cal State L.A., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      Materials include a contract agreement to reimburse CBEP for the Honors Program Faculty Training Institute for the Counseling Department at C.S.U.L.A. and a photo.
    - Naropa Institute, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Cal State L.A. conference, 1976 June (Box 35, Folder 24)
      Materials include a poster for the C.S.U.L.A. Conference on Humanistic Education which features Nelson's workshop, "City Building: Environmental Issues, Interaction, Future Thinking."
    - Summer workshop, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      Materials include two UCLA Extension applications for enrollment in the CBEP's "An Institute in Cooperative Curriculum Design for Teachers, Architects, Designers and Planners."
    - Ventura County Jr. High workshop, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - OE-HEW workshop, 1978 June (Box 35, Folder 27)